https://www.referee.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Resources
Covid and Officiating: Ready To Return?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Resources
Covid and Officiating: Ready To Return?
Referee
is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Referee Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Referee website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Referee collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Referee also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Referee . This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Referee for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Referee Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Referee public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Referee does not read any of your private online communications.
Referee encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Referee so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Referee is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Referee and Referee family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Referee collects and uses your personal information to operate the Referee Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Referee also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Referee and its affiliates. Referee may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Referee does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Referee may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Referee may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Referee , and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Referee does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Referee keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Referee , in order to determine what Referee services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Referee to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Referee Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Referee or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Referee ; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Referee , or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Referee Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Referee pages, or register with Referee site or services, a cookie helps Referee to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Referee Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Referee features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Referee services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Referee secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Referee secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Referee will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Referee encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Referee is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Referee welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Referee has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Referee at btopp@referee.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Advertising
This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia (“CafeMedia”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy
Top Free Guide Downloads
Covid and Officiating: Ready To Return?
Free Guides
Mental Performance A-Z
Free Guides
Find Your Officiating Personality
Free Guides
Next Level Softball Umpiring Free Email Series
Free Guides
Next Level Baseball Umpiring Free Email Series
Free Guides
Get Great Officiating Content Weekly
Subscribe to get the Referee.com Review every week plus periodic free training and special offers on the sports you officiate.
Success! Now check your email to confirm your subscription to the Referee.com Review.
There was an error submitting your subscription. Please try again.
Email Address
Subscribe
We won't send you spam. Everything we send is officiating specific because that's all we do.
Powered by ConvertKit
New Articles
Terry McAulay to receive 2021 Dave Dixon Louisiana Sports Leadership Award
News
70+ Free Officiating Video Sessions Available On Demand – WATCH NOW!
News
NFL: Week 14 referee assignments
News
NBA referees to have daily tests as part of new coronavirus...
News
Watch now: Minor league baseball umpire and Decatur resident Jen Pawol...
News
Referee, the world’s original sports officiating magazine, educates, challenges and inspires officials at all levels.Contact us: customerservice@referee.com
Home
Free Guides
Articles
Store
The Magazine
About Us
Advertising
Career Opportunities
Copyright © 2020 Referee Enterprises Inc.
